gimmebar.com 2017-10-07

# Gimme Bar : Privacy

Last updated: September 2, 2011

Gimme Bar, Inc. (“ **Gimme Bar** ,” “ **we** ” or “ **us** ”) is pleased to provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information we receive from you and other users of the Gimme Bar service, through our website located at **https://gimmebar.com** (the “ **Website** ”). Such service and the Website are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as the “ **Service**.” This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Service. Gimme Bar reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Website at http://www.gimmebar.com/privacy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Service will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.

## Information We Collect

We collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, geographic location and email address (your “ **Personal Information** ”), when you voluntarily provide it by registering for an account with us. You may also provide Personal Information to us in other ways, such as by requesting user support or submitting feedback through the feedback bar. **You may consider some of this information to be sensitive so you should choose carefully regarding whether and if you will use the Service.**

We also collect various categories of non-personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, information about our users’ hardware and usage of the Service, such as IP address, browser type, pages accessed, duration of visit, and use data. We also collect non-personal information passively through our website using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (also known as “web beacons”). When you visit our website, we may send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser, or recognize a cookie that is already on your machine. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, and to customize your experience. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, the Service may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. Also, please be aware that third parties may set cookies on your hard drive or use other means of passively collecting information about your use of their services or content. We do not have access to, or control over, these third-party means of passive data collection. We use non-personally identifiable information for purposes such as understanding trends in use of the Service. We also may prepare, publish, and disseminate reports, and other non-personally identifiable information derived therefrom to third parties. These third parties use this non-personally identifiable information for various purposes, including for marketing, and for demographics and engagement research.

## Use of Information

Gimme Bar collects and uses your information from you as follows:

Administration of the Service. Gimme Bar may use your information, including Personal Information, to administer the service, including to verify your authority to access the Service, to fulfill requests you may make, and to personalize your user experience. Gimme Bar may also observe your activities, preferences, and transactional data (such as your IP address and browser type) as well as content you have viewed during your use of the Service to personalize your user experience. We may use this data for any purpose unless we tell you otherwise in connection with providing the Service to you. Gimme Bar may also contract with various third parties who help us provide and maintain the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service’s features). In these cases, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your Personal Information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. 

## Development of the Service

In our mission to deliver more personalized search results to users, Gimme Bar will use your data anonymously in our own research to better understand search algorithms and improve our services, products, features and content. We may also share anonymous Personal Information with third-party researchers. Personal Information we share with a third party will be anonymous and not associated with your name or any identifying information provided by Gimme Bar.

## Technical and Administrative Support

Gimme Bar may use the information you provide in registration forms to notify you periodically about important changes to the Service (such as a change to this Privacy Policy or notice of a security breach), and new products and services and related features. 

## Marketing

When you provide Gimme Bar with Personal Information, we may communicate with you using the information you have given us to provide you with information we think may be of interest to you including marketing and promotional messages. For special offers and promotions we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of receiving further similar communications. 

## Service Partners

Through the Service, we may provide links to products and services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, service providers, partners, and other third parties (" **Service Partners** "). We and our Service Partners use your Personal Information to operate the Service and offer various features on, through or related to the Service. You should not disclose information to Gimme Bar that you do not want shared with third parties. We limit the Personal Information shared with these third parties to that which is necessary to carry out those functions, and we do not share your email address with any Service Partners. Unless you opt-out, our Service Partners may use such shared Personal Information to inform you, through the Service, of other products or services available from those Service Partners. 

## Legal Compliance; Enforcement

Gimme Bar will disclose your Personal Information as Gimme Bar believes in good faith is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority, to enforce our Terms of Service or any other agreements (including investigation of potential violations thereof), to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues, to protect the property and rights of Gimme Bar or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity Gimme Bar may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable. 

## Merger or Sale

Gimme Bar may disclose, transfer and assign your Personal Information upon a merger with another entity, a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of Gimme Bar’s stock or assets or upon any bankruptcy or other corporate reorganization.

You may opt-out of receiving some or all non-Service related communications by updating your account on the Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive any such communications, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of the communications sent to you, or update your account information.

We may receive personal information from third parties about their users, and may combine this information with Personal Information we maintain about you. If we do so, this policy governs the combined information. Depending on your account settings, certain information you provide may be available to other users.

## Controlling Your Personal Information

Gimme Bar may make available to users comment functionality, forums, message boards, and other interactive features. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) via such features, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Gimme Bar. Please do not post any personal information on the Website or otherwise through the Service that you expect to keep private. Please note that we will disclose the information you direct us to disclose, even if it contains Personal Information, for example if you share comments, geographic location, or other content or information on a third-party service, such as Facebook or Twitter. 

## Links

For your convenience, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties’ products or services. If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party’s privacy policy, and not the Gimme Bar privacy policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.

## Security

No data transmissions over the Internet or other networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security or integrity of any information you transmit to us. You transmit information to us at your own risk. Once we receive personal information, we make reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please be aware, however, that no security safeguards are completely secure. We cannot represent or guarantee that personal information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

## Referrals

As part of our referral program, we may request personally identifiable information of our users’ friends and family whom they think would like to receive information on the Service. The persons referred to us will be contacted only by Gimme Bar. We use and treat information our users provide about their referrals in the same way we use and treat information about users who register directly with Gimme Bar.

## Collection of Information From Children

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information relating to children. In the event that we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age without prior parental consent, we will take steps to promptly delete such information. By providing your personal information to Gimme Bar, through the Service, you represent that you are 13 years of age or older.

## International Visitors and Users

The Website is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the European Union (EU) or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  1. The use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
  2. The transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

## No Error-Free Performance

Gimme Bar does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it.

## Legal Notices

This Privacy Policy is subject to the terms in our Terms of Service, available for review at http://www.gimmebar.com/terms, including terms regarding limitations on damages and disclaimers of warranties. Our Terms of Service take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy. 

## Questions

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at:

Privacy Notice 509 Glenbrook Drive, Middletown, MD 21769 frank@fictivekin.com
